[
  {
    "question": "Fabric made from wood",
    "answer": "Lyocell"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many people are typically involved in creating a single haute couture dress?",
    "answer": "About 20"
  },
  {
    "question": "How old was Iris Apfel when she started her career in fashion?",
    "answer": "50 years old"
  },
  {
    "question": "How to reduce the ecological footprint?",
    "answer": "Reducing waste"
  },
  {
    "question": "How to wear a small bag?",
    "answer": "Crossbody"
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year was the Chanel brand founded?",
    "answer": "1910"
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year was the Louis Vuitton brand founded?",
    "answer": "1854"
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year was the first fashion show held?",
    "answer": "1903"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which city did the famous street style originate?",
    "answer": "New York"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which country is the Boa Vista Fashion Week held?",
    "answer": "Cape Verde"
  },
  {
    "question": "To which era does the Empire style belong?",
    "answer": "Napoleonic"
  },
  {
    "question": "Trend of the 2020s: sustainable fashion?",
    "answer": "Sustainable fashion"
  },
  {
    "question": "What T-shirts are currently in trend?",
    "answer": "Oversized"
  },
  {
    "question": "What accessories were worn during the Renaissance era?",
    "answer": "Pearls"
  },
  {
    "question": "What accessory is often used to clip a tie?",
    "answer": "Tie clip"
  },
  {
    "question": "What accessory often complements a suit?",
    "answer": "Cufflinks"
  },
  {
    "question": "What accessory was often used as a brooch in ancient times?",
    "answer": "fibula"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are ancient gems called?",
    "answer": "cameo"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are high fashion models called?",
    "answer": "Haute couture"
  },
  {
    "question": "What are long earrings called?",
    "answer": "Threader earrings"
  },
  {
    "question": "What asymmetrical element is often added to a dress?",
    "answer": "Hem"
  },
  {
    "question": "What brand was primarily associated with Grace Kelly?",
    "answer": "Hermès"
  },
  {
    "question": "What characteristics are associated with haute couture?",
    "answer": "Uniqueness"
  },
  {
    "question": "What clothing is most commonly chosen for sports activities in 2023?",
    "answer": "Leggings"
  },
  {
    "question": "What clothing is worn for a layered look?",
    "answer": "Cardigan"
  },
  {
    "question": "What clothing item is traditionally paired with a pencil skirt?",
    "answer": "Blouse"
  },
  {
    "question": "What clothing items are characteristic of Parisian fashion?",
    "answer": "Scarves, berets"
  },
  {
    "question": "What clothing style became fashionable in the 1940s?",
    "answer": "New Look"
  },
  {
    "question": "What clothing style did Yohji Yamamoto introduce?",
    "answer": "Avant-garde"
  },
  {
    "question": "What clothing style includes retro elements?",
    "answer": "Retro chic"
  },
  {
    "question": "What did the unisex style symbolize in the 1990s?",
    "answer": "Bombers"
  },
  {
    "question": "What do 2D printers print?",
    "answer": "Documents"
  },
  {
    "question": "What do men wear to formal events?",
    "answer": "Tuxedo"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does 'sustainable fashion' mean?",
    "answer": "Environmentally friendly"
  },
  {
    "question": "What does 'патентная кожа' mean?",
    "answer": "Patent leather"
  },
  {
    "question": "What dresses were in fashion during the Victorian era?",
    "answer": "Corsets and crinolines"
  },
  {
    "question": "What event annually attracts many celebrities?",
    "answer": "Met Gala"
  },
  {
    "question": "What event takes place in Los Angeles and is dedicated to street fashion?",
    "answer": "Made LA"
  },
  {
    "question": "What fashion show is held in June and January in London?",
    "answer": "London Fashion Week Men's"
  },
  {
    "question": "What fashion style was popular in the 19th century?",
    "answer": "Victorian"
  },
  {
    "question": "What footwear is associated with the Gothic style?",
    "answer": "Doc Martens"
  },
  {
    "question": "What footwear is popular in Japan?",
    "answer": "Tabi"
  },
  {
    "question": "What helps reduce the carbon footprint in fashion?",
    "answer": "Recycling fabrics"
  },
  {
    "question": "What indicates that a suit belongs to the sports style?",
    "answer": "Sport stripes"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 'biodegradable clothing'?",
    "answer": "Naturally decomposes"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is 'upcycling'?",
    "answer": "Repurposing items"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is VR technology used for in fashion?",
    "answer": "Virtual fitting"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is a trilby?",
    "answer": "Hat"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is considered the classic length for a coat?",
    "answer": "Three quarters"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is important in a school uniform?",
    "answer": "Comfort and appearance"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the decorative pattern on fabric called?",
    "answer": "Embroidery"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the hairstyle of the 1920s called?",
    "answer": "Bob"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the main brand of Japanese designer Yohji called?",
    "answer": "Yohji Yamamoto"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the material made from orange peel called?",
    "answer": "Orange Fiber"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the most prestigious event in the fashion world?",
    "answer": "Paris Fashion Week"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of a ring with a seal?",
    "answer": "Signet ring"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of clothing that displays notifications?",
    "answer": "Interactive clothing"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of men's shoes with a pointed toe?",
    "answer": "Oxfords"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the Gucci men's collection for Spring-Summer 2020?",
    "answer": "Epilogue"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the clothing used to accentuate the waist?",
    "answer": "Corset"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the creative director of Balenciaga?",
    "answer": "Demna Gvasalia"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the fabric that changes color?",
    "answer": "Chameleon"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the fabric that reacts to light?",
    "answer": "Photoreactive"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the fashion week on Sixth Avenue in New York?",
    "answer": "Made Fashion Week"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the mesh fabric used for sportswear?",
    "answer": "Mesh"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of traditional English shoes with perforations?",
    "answer": "Brogues"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the process of creating clothing using sensors called?",
    "answer": "Smart fabrics"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the process of creating new clothes from old ones called?",
    "answer": "Upcycling"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the process of decorating metals called?",
    "answer": "Engraving"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the reduction of CO2 emissions associated with?",
    "answer": "Eco-fashion goal"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the style called that involves wearing multiple layers of clothing?",
    "answer": "Layering"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the substance used to create an elegant shine in varnishes and paints called?",
    "answer": "Mother-of-pearl"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the technique of giving new life to old items called?",
    "answer": "Upcycling"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is used in jewelry to create patterns?",
    "answer": "Enamel"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is usually chosen for stylish evening outfits?",
    "answer": "Tuxedo"
  },
  {
    "question": "What material is most commonly used for outerwear?",
    "answer": "Neoprene"
  },
  {
    "question": "What music genre does singer Taylor Swift prefer?",
    "answer": "Pop"
  },
  {
    "question": "What pants should you wear in the rain?",
    "answer": "Waterproof"
  },
  {
    "question": "What pattern is popular for blazers?",
    "answer": "Glen check"
  },
  {
    "question": "What piece of jewelry does a princess wear?",
    "answer": "Tiara"
  },
  {
    "question": "What popular pattern is used in jewelry?",
    "answer": "Fleur-de-lis"
  },
  {
    "question": "What role did Pierre Cardin play in 1960s fashion?",
    "answer": "Space fashion"
  },
  {
    "question": "What shoes automatically tighten on the foot?",
    "answer": "Nike Adapt"
  },
  {
    "question": "What silhouette of suits was trendy?",
    "answer": "Fitted"
  },
  {
    "question": "What strategy helps reduce waste in fashion?",
    "answer": "Upcycling"
  },
  {
    "question": "What style did Elsa Schiaparelli adhere to in her works?",
    "answer": "Surrealism"
  },
  {
    "question": "What style of clothing is most often chosen for school?",
    "answer": "Classic"
  },
  {
    "question": "What style of necklace did Egyptian pharaohs wear?",
    "answer": "Pectoral necklace"
  },
  {
    "question": "What style of suits was popular in the 1990s?",
    "answer": "Casual"
  },
  {
    "question": "What style was popular for evening wear in 2023?",
    "answer": "Retro glamour"
  },
  {
    "question": "What style was popular in the early 19th century?",
    "answer": "Classicism"
  },
  {
    "question": "What technology allows the creation of smart textiles?",
    "answer": "E-textiles"
  },
  {
    "question": "What technology helps reduce textile waste?",
    "answer": "Zero-Waste Technology"
  },
  {
    "question": "What technology is used in smart sneakers?",
    "answer": "Piezo sensors"
  },
  {
    "question": "What technology is used to create interactive fashion shows?",
    "answer": "VR"
  },
  {
    "question": "What technology is used to reduce waste?",
    "answer": "Zero-waste manufacturing"
  },
  {
    "question": "What trend contributes to more conscious consumption in fashion?",
    "answer": "Conscious consumption"
  },
  {
    "question": "What trend dominates street fashion at shows?",
    "answer": "Mixing of styles"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of belt is worn over the shoulder?",
    "answer": "Bandolier"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of boots are often worn in the summer?",
    "answer": "Mesh boots"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of clothing became a popular element of street fashion since the 1980s?",
    "answer": "Hoodie"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of clothing can change color?",
    "answer": "Smart"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of clothing is popular in Japanese street fashion?",
    "answer": "Harajuku"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of collar on a shirt is considered classic?",
    "answer": "Kent"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of footwear became popular in the 1960s?",
    "answer": "platform boots"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of footwear can change size?",
    "answer": "Adaptive sneakers"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of footwear did the Vikings wear?",
    "answer": "Husos"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of footwear is associated with luxury leisure?",
    "answer": "Loafers"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of footwear is suitable for rock climbing?",
    "answer": "Climbing shoes"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of glasses were popular in fashion during the 1960s?",
    "answer": "Cat-eye glasses"
  },
  {
    "question": "What type of pants is suitable for the summer season?",
    "answer": "Linen"
  },
  {
    "question": "What very expensive and rare stone did kings wear?",
    "answer": "diamond"
  },
  {
    "question": "When did Ralph Lauren start his career?",
    "answer": "1967"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which French designer became famous for his avant-garde collections?",
    "answer": "Jean-Paul Gaultier"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Japanese brand is famous for its futuristic shows?",
    "answer": "Issey Miyake"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Japanese brand is known for innovative streetwear?",
    "answer": "A Bathing Ape"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Prada collection became a symbol of minimalism?",
    "answer": "Minimal Baroque"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which Spanish designer is known for their experimental forms?",
    "answer": "Balenciaga"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which actress is known for her outfits at the Met Gala?",
    "answer": "Rihanna"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which brand created the concert costumes for Beyoncé's 'Formation' tour?",
    "answer": "Balmain"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which brand created the dresses for the movie 'Sex and the City'?",
    "answer": "Vivienne Westwood"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which brand created the famous red shoes with a bow?",
    "answer": "Valentino"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which brand created the iconic Panerai watches?",
    "answer": "Officine Panerai"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which brand did Audrey Hepburn wear in the movie 'Breakfast at Tiffany's'?",
    "answer": "Givenchy"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which brand does Bella Hadid prefer?",
    "answer": "Balenciaga"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which brand introduced the trend for premium sneakers?",
    "answer": "Balenciaga"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which brand introduces 'Nude' shoes?",
    "answer": "Christian Louboutin"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which brand is famous for its briefcases and business accessories?",
    "answer": "Montblanc"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which brand is famous for its fedoras?",
    "answer": "Borsalino"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which brand is famous for its footwear?",
    "answer": "Cole Haan"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which brand is famous for its linen suits?",
    "answer": "Ermenegildo Zegna"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which brand is famous for producing suitcases and bags?",
    "answer": "Louis Vuitton"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which brand is founded on the principles of sustainable fashion and ecology?",
    "answer": "Stella McCartney"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which brand is known for its fashion shows, famous performances, and innovations?",
    "answer": "Alexander McQueen"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which brand is known for its iconic striped sweaters?",
    "answer": "Comme des Garçons"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which brand is known for its minimalist design solutions?",
    "answer": "Celine"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which brand is known for its unusual hats?",
    "answer": "Philip Treacy"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which brand is renowned for its elegant and stylish evening gowns?",
    "answer": "Oscar de la Renta"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which brand is renowned for its luxurious leather goods, including belts and wallets?",
    "answer": "Hermès"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which brand often collaborates with artists to create unique collections?",
    "answer": "Louis Vuitton"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which brand organizes Paris Fashion Week?",
    "answer": "FHCM"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which brand organizes its show in Monte Carlo?",
    "answer": "Christian Dior"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which brand presented an 'homage' to the elements?",
    "answer": "Chanel"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which brand produces clothing in the working-class style?",
    "answer": "Carhartt"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which brand produces clothing with patriotic motifs?",
    "answer": "Patriotic"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which brand produces the legendary Baracuta jacket models?",
    "answer": "Baracuta"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which brand released the first deodorant?",
    "answer": "Mum"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which brand released the first heart-shaped glasses?",
    "answer": "Lolita"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which brand specializes in loafers?",
    "answer": "Gucci"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which brand was the first to introduce the grunge style?",
    "answer": "Comme des Garçons"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which brand was the first to use eco-leather?",
    "answer": "Stella McCartney"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which brand's watches are considered luxury?",
    "answer": "Rolex"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which clothing manufacturing method supports sustainable fashion?",
    "answer": "Slow fashion"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which company sponsored the Met Gala in 2022?",
    "answer": "Gucci"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which company uses mushrooms to create materials?",
    "answer": "MycoWorks"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which company was the first to start producing 3D-printed clothing?",
    "answer": "Adidas"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which decade popularized vinyl fabrics in fashion?",
    "answer": "1960s"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which design practice minimizes waste?",
    "answer": "Zero waste"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which designer became famous for the debut collection 'Stairway to Heaven'?",
    "answer": "Giorgio Armani"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which designer collection included suits made from recycled plastic?",
    "answer": "Eco-collection"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which designer created dresses from metal and plastic?",
    "answer": "Paco Rabanne"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which designer created the famous non-logo T-shirts?",
    "answer": "Demna Gvasalia"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which designer created the first ready-to-wear collection in the 1960s?",
    "answer": "Yves Saint Laurent"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which designer created the iconic dresses for Jacqueline Kennedy?",
    "answer": "Oleg Cassini"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which designer created the original costumes for the Tame Impala tour?",
    "answer": "Alexander Wang"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which designer has always supported minimalism in their collections?",
    "answer": "Yohji Yamamoto"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which designer introduced elastic fabrics into Haute Couture?",
    "answer": "Azzedine Alaïa"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which designer is known for collaborations with famous musicians?",
    "answer": "Rick Owens"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which designer is known for his innovations in men's fashion?",
    "answer": "Thom Browne"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which designer is known for their avant-garde approaches in fashion?",
    "answer": "Martin Margiela"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which designer is known for their red carpet dresses?",
    "answer": "Elie Saab"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which designer is known for their unusual experimental forms in clothing?",
    "answer": "Rei Kawakubo"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which designer most frequently dressed Lady Gaga?",
    "answer": "Alexander McQueen"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which designer was the first to introduce the concept of unisex in their collections?",
    "answer": "Jean-Paul Gaultier"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which designer was the first to use plexiglass in shoes?",
    "answer": "Salvatore Ferragamo"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which device creates digital objects?",
    "answer": "3D printer"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which dress did Blake Lively choose for the Met Gala 2018?",
    "answer": "Versace"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which dress style accentuates the figure?",
    "answer": "empire"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which fabric is rarely used in high fashion?",
    "answer": "Denim"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which fabric responds to body temperature?",
    "answer": "Thermo fabric"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which fabric was popular in the 1990s?",
    "answer": "Pleats"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which fashion brand is named after a Spanish city?",
    "answer": "Balenciaga"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which fashion brand released a collection of bags with balloons?",
    "answer": "Anya Hindmarch"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which fashion brand was founded by Pierre Balmain?",
    "answer": "Balmain"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which fashion company is eco-friendly?",
    "answer": "Patagonia"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which fashion designer introduced asymmetrical hemlines?",
    "answer": "Thierry Mugler"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which fashion designer was the first to introduce the concept of 'ready-to-wear'?",
    "answer": "Pierre Cardin"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which fashion era was inspired by Queen Victoria?",
    "answer": "Victorian"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which fashion house creates collections inspired by architecture?",
    "answer": "Iris van Herpen"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which fashion house used augmented reality in their 2018 show?",
    "answer": "Burberry"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which fashion trend includes sports elements with everyday clothing?",
    "answer": "Gorpcore"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which gemstone is nicknamed 'the tear of the gods'?",
    "answer": "opal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which gemstone is often set in gold?",
    "answer": "Ruby"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which gemstone is often used to adorn high-end watches?",
    "answer": "diamond"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is biodegradable?",
    "answer": "Hemp"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following trends is an eco-trend?",
    "answer": "Recycled materials"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which sensor is often used to track user activity?",
    "answer": "Accelerometer"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which shirts became popular this season?",
    "answer": "Linen"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which silhouette became popular in the 1950s?",
    "answer": "Hourglass"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which stone is considered a symbol of wisdom?",
    "answer": "Amethyst"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which street fashion item is popular among artists?",
    "answer": "Beret"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which street fashion style is associated with radical political movements and self-expression?",
    "answer": "Punk"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which style came back into fashion in spring 2023?",
    "answer": "Retro"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which style combines comfort and aesthetics?",
    "answer": "Sport-chic"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which style includes the cinema style?",
    "answer": "Glamour"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which technology reduces waste?",
    "answer": "3D printing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which type of footwear fits the term 'retro style'?",
    "answer": "Clogs"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which type of footwear is characterized by an open toe and heel?",
    "answer": "Mules"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which type of production is less harmful to nature?",
    "answer": "Handmade"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who annually chairs the organizing committee of the Met Gala?",
    "answer": "Anna Wintour"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who became a style icon in boho-chic?",
    "answer": "Sienna Miller"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who created the brand Kenzo?",
    "answer": "Kenzo Takada"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who created the brand L.A.M.B.?",
    "answer": "Gwen Stefani"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who designed the costumes for the movie 'The Fifth Element'?",
    "answer": "Jean-Paul Gaultier"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who first popularized the bomber jacket?",
    "answer": "U.S. Air Force"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who founded the CFDA foundation?",
    "answer": "Eleanor Lambert"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who founded the fashion house Hermès?",
    "answer": "Thierry Hermès"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who has been the creative director of Gucci since 2015?",
    "answer": "Alessandro Michele"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who introduced the fashion for lace in the Victorian era?",
    "answer": "Queen Victoria"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who introduced the fashion for ripped jeans?",
    "answer": "Vivienne Westwood"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who introduced the unisex style in fashion?",
    "answer": "André Courrèges"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is known for theatrical shows?",
    "answer": "Jean-Paul Gaultier"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is known for using architecture in fashion?",
    "answer": "Iris van Herpen"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is referred to as the 'icon of high fashion'?",
    "answer": "Karl Lagerfeld"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the creative director of Dior?",
    "answer": "Maria Grazia Chiuri"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the designer known for their avant-garde work?",
    "answer": "Rei Kawakubo"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the designer of the brand 'JW Anderson'?",
    "answer": "Jonathan Anderson"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the head of the Givenchy brand in 2023?",
    "answer": "Matthew Williams"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is the organizer of Paris Haute Couture Week?",
    "answer": "Chambre Syndicale"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who led the fashion house Balenciaga before Demna Gvasalia?",
    "answer": "Alexander Wang"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who oversees the organization of Tokyo Fashion Week?",
    "answer": "Japan Fashion Association"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who popularized the mini-skirt?",
    "answer": "Mary Quant"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was at the origins of the popularity of the fashion house 'Valentino'?",
    "answer": "Valentino Garavani"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was named Designer of the Year at the British Fashion Awards 2018?",
    "answer": "Kim Jones"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the artistic director of Dior in 1989?",
    "answer": "Gianfranco Ferré"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the creative director of Chanel from 1983 to 2019?",
    "answer": "Karl Lagerfeld"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the designer of Björk's famous swan dress?",
    "answer": "Marjan Pejoski"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the main fashion trendsetter of the 1950s?",
    "answer": "Marlene Dietrich"
  },
  {
    "question": "Year of release of the first smartwatches:",
    "answer": "2012"
  }
]